hi I'm Joseph Dominguez I'm a cyber
insurance specialist and on this channel
I'm going to teach you about
cybersecurity and cyber insurance and
how it can protect your business
[Music]
[Applause]
you guys here's another question I get
all the time how do I know what is the
right cyber insurance policy for my
business well the answer is you don't
know and you should talk to a cyber
insurance specialist what they're going
to do is they're going to help you
decide which company is the best because
every company varies because they all
have different types of products and you
as a business owner will have different
types of needs so the needs of business
a and the needs of business B can be
greatly different so one of the main
factors is does your company store
personally identifiable information or
your customers information do you have
on your database do you have credit card
numbers date of birth social security
numbers address driver's license all
those things so if your system was
hacked can that information be taken or
are you a an office that doesn't store
any information maybe like a sales
office that you're just selling a
product so if you don't have that
information
you'll need a different type of policy
so as cybersecurity experts and
specialists can help determine what
those things are they will evaluate your
risk and make sure that you're fully
protected so they will also then go out
to the market and check with all the
different companies and carriers such as
Chubb and AIG and travelers an ass took
a marine and many many a more they will
read those policies find out what the
coverages are on those policies how it
specifically it can be tailor-made and
customized for your specific needs and
then also of course for the right price
so the answer is how you know which
cyber company is good for you consult
with a specialist and they'll help you
to determine that subscribe to this
channel to learn more on cybersecurity
and cyber insurance bring the
notification film and check
[Music]
you